<movie>
<title>The Marvels</title>
<year>2023</year>
<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
<director>Nia DaCosta</director>
<summary>Carol Danvers, aka Captain Marvel, has reclaimed her identity from the tyrannical Kree and taken revenge on the Supreme Intelligence. However, unintended consequences see her shouldering the burden of a destabilized universe. When her duties send her to an anomalous wormhole linked to a Kree revolut… MORE
</summary>
<poster></poster>
</movie>
<movie>
<title>Parasite</title>
<year>2019</year>
<genre>Thriller, Comedy</genre>
<director>Bong Joon-Ho</director>
<summary>Greed and class discrimination threaten the newly formed symbiotic relationship between the wealthy Park family and the destitute Kim clan.</summary>
<poster></poster>
</movie>
<movie>
<title>Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse</title>
<year>2023</year>
<genre>Action, Sci-fi</genre>
<director>Joaquim Dos Santos, Kemp Powers, Justin K. Thompson</director>
<summary>After reuniting with Gwen Stacy, Brooklyn's full-time, friendly neighborhood Spider-Man is catapulted across the Multiverse, where he encounters a team of Spider-People charged with protecting its very existence. However, when the heroes clash on how to handle a new threat, Miles finds himself pitted against the other Spiders. He must soon redefine what it means to be a hero so he can save the people he loves most.</summary>
<poster></poster>
</movie>
<movie>
<title>Incantation</title>
<year>2022</year>
<genre>Horror, Documentary</genre>
<director>Kevin Ko</director>
<summary>Six years ago, Li Ronan is cursed after breaking a religious taboo; now, she must protect her daughter from the consequences of her actions.</summary>
<poster></poster>
</movie>
<movie>
<title>Anyone But You</title>
<year>2023</year>
<genre>2023</genre>
<director>Will Gluck, Joe Roth, Jeff Kirschenbaum</director>
<summary>Despite having an amazing first date, Bea and Ben's initial attraction quickly turns sour. When they unexpectedly find themselves at a destination wedding in Australia, the pair pretend to be the perfect couple to keep up appearances.
</summary>
<poster></poster>
</movie>